Oh Somebody's not
Speaker 1: feeling
Speaker 2: good We can
Speaker 1: get we can get our doctors back there
to help out I
Does
Speaker 1: somebody want to go to my doctor's office and just have them? You guys know where the doctor's
office is? Here's it. Just go
Speaker 3: through the palm doors. It's right
-- right next to
Speaker 3: the map room. To
Speaker 4: free families
from the
Speaker 4: pervasive fear that one illness -- The
guys must find me not alone.
I got
Speaker 5: you. You're okay. This happens when I talk
too long.
Speaker 7: Jay! President Obama pays tribute to injured soldier
Speaker 8: Corey Ransford.
Speaker 9: Nice to meet you.
Speaker 8: Corey is here tonight. And like the army
Speaker 10: he loves, like
Speaker 11: the America he serves,
Speaker 11: Sergeant first-class Coy Rimsburg never gives up and he does not quit.
I don't know what the best is smooth.
Speaker 12: I'll go in the
way you want. I don't
Speaker 13: know what the best is smooth while boarding the way
you want. I don't know what the best is smooth while boarding the way you want. I don't know what the best is smooth.
Speaker 14: Obama's clues
Speaker 15: were completely solved by the way.
It must be great, it's my feeling, now I saw you. Yeah, I knew I was still up by standing strong. There's nothing in the room with me. - Woo! Woo!
Speaker 16: Woo! Woo! Woo! Woo! Woo!
- Job
Speaker 17: site safety manager, Crystal Chavez, her heart has been taken for emotions.
Speaker 18: - I just happened to glance at the door, and I was like--
Speaker 18: But
Speaker 19: I said I wasn't going to cry if I had the opportunity to meet him. And my mother would always say, "Oh, please, tell him I love him." And my wife said, "Mom, I'm not going to meet him." And then, when he asked me... We can write him a letter.
Speaker 20: You want to write him a letter? Dear Mr. President, my name is Camille McRae.
I am
Speaker 20: located just like you. I don't want you to leave the White
Speaker 21: House. You're a mother,
Speaker 20: that's the one.
Speaker 22: Hello, everybody. What?
Speaker 23: As
Speaker 24: we approach Veterans Day, I wanted to stop by and just say
--
Speaker 25: Barack Obama's prized his plane full of veterans arriving in Washington.
Speaker 26: The President: The time I got to see a president, it was with
Speaker 27: Carol Ford. How about that? The President:
Speaker 28: Okay, where are we going? The President: You guys call our number? Is that the
deal?
Speaker 28: Bring those up. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I got to pay for them all. That's
the
Speaker 29: deal. This is mine. That's yours. Hold on, because I got to pay for
Speaker 30: them. Hey, Prince, what's going on, man?
Speaker 31: Perfect.
Speaker 31: - Oh, oh, red, red, red, red. - Simple man, you gotta give me a high five. - Oh, boy. - You are,
Speaker 33: you look so powerful. - High five. - That's, oh, oh, you were so strong, you knocked me over. - High fives,
Speaker 34: high fives, high
Speaker 35: fives. - Give me high
Speaker 36: fives. Of course, we're gonna pose for a picture.
Speaker 36: Oh,
Speaker 38: thank you
so much for being here. - Hi.
Speaker 39: Bitch. Love. Love.
- Hey, you're done, right?
Speaker 40: - Oh my God, how are you doing that? - I'm so sorry. - Oh, I'm a lot of it.
Speaker 42: - That's how it's
gonna be on the
Speaker 42: show. - Oh! -
And I signed it on
Speaker 43: the back. So in case you become president, you already have one. You don't even have
Speaker 44: to get a new one. You'll be all set.
-
Speaker 44: Thank you. -
You're welcome. - I
Speaker 45: have to say
a
Speaker 46: lot of people
Speaker 47: hate you
and
The
Speaker 47: Press: And why they both
Speaker 48: love you and God is loving
Speaker 49: you. The President: That's
what I'm talking
Speaker 49: about. Well,
Speaker 43: now, first of all, I did get elected president, so not everybody hates me now. I don't want you to -- you get some of the credit when things go good and when things are going tough, then, you know, you're going to get some of the blame and that's part of the job.
Speaker 43: I'm a pretty tough guy. Are you a tough guy? You look like you're pretty tough. And so you just got to keep on going even when folks are criticizing you because as long as you know that you're doing it for other people. All right? So thank you. You're a fine young man. I appreciate you.